musclexposed.com 2017-06-07

# Privacy ‹ muscleXposed – Huge Buffed Female Muscle

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. We do not collect any customer information for the purpose of selling, renting, or any other form of distribution. Please see our payment processor’s Privacy Policy concerning collected information. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on muscleXposed.com website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name Address Email address Phone number.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your account using the password you selected. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
